<helpDefinition>
    <title>
        Jasmine Help
    </title>
    <componentContainer>
        <LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/EC-Jasmine/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
        <div class="help" >
            <h1 class="help">
	                    Jasmine
	                </h1>
	                <h2 class="help">
	                    Overview
	                </h2>
	                <p class="help">
	                    Jasmine is a small JavaScript testing DOM-less framework. It is a successor of
	                    JsUnit and it can be downloaded and published on a server to execute test runners.
	                    Also, it can be executed through its Ruby gem, which makes it easier to use for
	                    continuous integration.
	                    </p>
	                    <p class="help">
	                    <b>Note:</b> You must install the Ruby environment as well as the Jasmine gem and its dependencies (rake, rack, win32console, rspec, selenium-rc).
	                    </p>
	                    <p class="help">
			                <b>Supported tool version</b><br>
			                This plugin was developed and tested with Jasmine version 1.0.1.
			                </p>
	                <h2 class="help">
	                    Configuration
	                </h2>
	                <p class="help">
	                    You do not need to configure the plugin before using it.
	                </p>
	                <h2 class="help">
	                    Using the Plugin
	                </h2>
	                <p class="help">
	    			See the <a href="/commander/link/showHelp?page=plugins&amp;section=using">Commander online help system</a> for details about how to use this plugin within a procedure.
	    			</p>
	    			<p class="help">
	    			When you provide information for this plugin, fill-in the fields as follows:
	    			</p>
	                            <ul>
	                                <li><b>Rakefile location</b> - Provide the absolute path to the rakefile that contains the Jasmine tasks to be executed.</li>
	                                <li><b>Type of execution</b> - Select the target to execute for the Rake invocation, either jasmine or jasmine:ci for default and Selenium modes, respectively.</li>
	                                <li><b>Additional Rake Commands</b> - Provide any additional commands to execute for Rake.</li>
	                                <li><b>Working directory</b> - Indicate the desired working directory. Leave blank to use the default workspace.</li>
	                            </ul>
	                        </li>
	                    </ol>
	                <p></p>
	    
	                <h2 class="help">
	                    Additional Information
	                </h2>
	                <ul>
	                    <li><a href="http://pivotal.github.com/jasmine/">Jasmine</a></li>
            </ul>
        </div>
    </componentContainer>
</helpDefinition>

