  <helpDefinition>
  <title>Splint Help</title>
  <componentContainer>
    <LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/EC-Splint/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
    <div class="help" >
      <h1 class="help">Splint</h1>
      <h2 class="help">Overview</h2>
      <p class="help">
Splint is a tool that does static analysis on C programs for security 
vulnerabilities and coding mistakes. With minimal effort, Splint can be 
used as a better lint. If additional effort is invested adding annotations 
to programs, Splint can perform stronger checking than can be done by any 
standard lint. Initially, it is only available for Linux, but an older version 
was developed specifically for Windows.</p>


      <h2 class="help">Configuration</h2>
    
    <p class="help">You do not need to configure the plugin before using it.</p>

     <h2 class="help">Using the Plugin</h2>

      <p class="help">
      When creating a procedure, in the Steps tab, click the <B>Add Step</B> button and select 
      <b>splint</b> from the <b>Code Analysis Tools</b> category. Complete the following parameters: 
      <ul>
          
        <li>Splint installation path - Path to the splint installation path, 
        default value is splint, if Windows version is used, you should point to the 
        absolute path of splint.exe</li>
        
        <li>Target to analyze - Path of the target to analyze. 
        It can be a file or a pattern.</li>
        
        <li>Specification files path - Add directory to path search for .lcl 
        specification files.</li>
        
        <li>Options file - Load options from a file. If this flag is used from 
        the command line, the default ~/.splintrc file is not loaded. 
        This flag may be used in an options file to load in another 
        options file. </li>
        
        <li>Add directory to path - Add directory to path searched for C include files. 
        Note there is no space after the I, to be consistent with C preprocessor 
        flags.</li>
        
        <li>Show scan - Show file names are they are processed.</li>
        
        <li>Show stats - Display number of lines processed and checking time.</li>
        
        <li>Show summary - Show a summary of all errors reported and suppressed. 
        Counts of suppressed errors are not necessarily correct since turning 
        a flag off may prevent some checking from being done to save computation, 
        and errors that are not reported may propagate differently from when 
        they are reported.</li>
        
        <li>Additional commands - Additional general commands for Splint. 
        User-defined commands, to be written as if if they were typed in 
        the console.</li>
        
        <li>Working directory - Desired working directory, leaving this blank uses 
        the default workspace.</li>
        
      </ul>
      
      </p>

      <h2 class="help">Additional Information</h2>
      <ul>
          <li> <a href="http://www.splint.org">Splint's home page</a> </li>
      </ul>
      
    </div>
  </componentContainer>
 </helpDefinition>

