  <helpDefinition>
  <title>Jasmine Help</title>
  <componentContainer>
    <LINK REL="StyleSheet" HREF="../../plugins/EC-Jasmine/pluginhelp.css" TYPE="text/css" MEDIA="screen"/>
    <div class="help" >
      <h1 class="help">Jasmine</h1>
      <h2 class="help">Overview</h2>
      <p class="help">
Jasmine is a small Javascript testing DOM-less framework. It is a successor of 
JSUnit and it can be downloaded and published on a server to execute test runners. 
Also, it can be executed through its ruby gem, which makes it a lot easier to use for 
continuous integration.
<br/>
It was created by authors of jsUnit and Screw.Unit. Using a different approach than JSpec, 
Jasmine uses Java Script syntax to the maximum instead of trying to mimic Ruby.</p>


      <h2 class="help">Configuration</h2>
    
    <p class="help">You do not need to configure the plugin before using it. 
    However, you must install the Ruby environment as well as the Jasmine gem and its dependencies (rake, rack, win32console, rspec, selenium-rc).</p>

     <h2 class="help">Using the Plugin</h2>
     
      <p class="help">
      When creating a procedure, do the following:
      
      <ol>
      <li>Click the <b>Add Step</b> on the <b>Steps</b> panel.</li>
      <li>Select <b>jasmine</b> from the <b>Test Tools</b> category.</li> 
      <li>Complete the appropriate fields. The following fields are available: 
      <ul>
          
        <li>Rakefile location - Absolute path to the rakefile that has the Jasmine tasks to be executed.</li>
        
        <li>Type of execution - Selects the target that will be executed for the Rake invocation, either <b>jasmine</b> or <b>jasmine:ci</b> for the default mode and Selenium respectively.</li>
        
        <li>Additional Rake Commands - Additional commands to be executed for Rake.</li>
        
        <li>Working directory - Desired working directory. Leave blank to use 
        the default workspace.</li>
        
      </ul>
      </li>
      </ol>
      </p>

      <h2 class="help">Additional Information</h2>
      <ul>
          <li> <a href="http://pivotal.github.com/jasmine/">Jasmine</a> </li>
      </ul>
      
      
    </div>
  </componentContainer>
 </helpDefinition>

